(Penny:)-Good night.
-Mm-hm.
(Amy:)It was rather flattering
to have strangers send us drinks.
(Bernadette:)Yeah, that felt nice.
(Amy:)Maybe tomorrow morning
we put on some hot pants
(Amy:)and see if we can score us
some free omelets.
So, hypothetically, if we
were to have gone with them,
(Bernadette:)which one would you have picked?
(Amy:)I think I would have gone with the
short one with the goofy haircut.
(Bernadette:)Oh, good, 'cause I liked
the tall thin one.
(Bernadette:)He seemed intelligent,
kind of a loner,
(Bernadette:)maybe a little sexually
inexperienced,
(Bernadette:)like I'd have
to teach him a thing or two.
(Amy:)Not my guy.
I caught him staring at my rack.
(Amy:)It'd be nice to be with a man
(Amy:)who wants to know
what's underneath my cardigan.